Ah! Ah, that feels
so good!
Oh, lucky me.
Coffee and a live sex show.
Oh, I'm sorry, what?
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry. Nothing.
I was just reading to Emma.
From Cosmo?
Yeah, yeah, it's, uh...
"Climax Your Way
to Better Skin."
So, I have
to go shopping today,
which is
my least favorite thing.
I'm so bad
at picking out clothes.
So, you need someone
who knows fashion
to, uh, tell you
what looks good.
Not me, not me,
not me, not me, not me...
Oh, hey, Rach?
Yeah?
Maybe you could take
Charlie shopping.
Oh, well...
I'm sure you have
better things to do.
Are you kidding?
Rachel loves to shop.
And she has great taste.
Yeah, she's the one
that taught me
you don't wear white
after Labor Day,
and that you always,
always, always have
to put on underwear
when you're trying
on clothes.
If you have the time,
I'd really appreciate
the help.
Okay, yeah, let's, let's shop.
Okay, you are going
to come back
with some very
classy clothes.
( chuckling )
And some slutty
lingerie-- slutty.
( chuckling ):
Okay, great.
All right, bye.
Pain in the ass.
That's off, right?
What's the matter,
Pheebs?
Oh, Mike's sister
just invited me
to a party tonight,
and he's going
to be there.
And she was, like,
"Oh, don't worry.
I asked him, and he's
totally okay with seeing you."
So, now I have to go
so he'll think
that I'm totally okay
with seeing him.
Which you're not because
you're totally hung up on him.
Exactly.
And you're going to want him
to eat his heart out,
so you're going to
have to look fabulous.
I didn't even think about that.
Ah, sexual politics!
Hey, Pheebs, I'm
taking Charlie shopping.
Why don't you come,
and I'll help you
find something?
Okay, that would be great.
Oh, isn't that nice?
The three of you
trying on slutty
lingerie together.
That's not
what we're going to do.
Why would you ruin it?
Who was I hurting?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Wow.
Fortunately,
she has a very pretty face.
Oh, I still
can't believe this.
My uterus is
an inhospitable environment?
I've always tried so hard
to be a good hostess.
Well, I can't believe
my sperm have low motility,
because let me tell you,
while I was growing up,
they sure seemed to be
in a hurry to get places.
Hi, there.
Hi.
I'm sorry there wasn't better
news from your tests last week,
but I wanted to talk to you
about your options.
Okay.
Well, first of all,
even though
your chances of conceiving
through natural means
aren't great, you never know,
so keep having sex
on a regular basis.
Aw, damn it!
Don't worry,
after a while,
you'll tune it out.
Well, given
your situation,
the options with the greatest
chances for success
would be surrogacy
or insemination
using a sperm donor.
Okay.
And of course,
if you feel that neither
of those is right for you,
you could always adopt.
Is that a hint?
Because we love you,
Dr. Connolly,
but we don't think
we want you to be our child.
Wow, talk about
an inhospitable environment.
Hi.
Okay, are you ready
to go pick up Phoebe
and go shopping?
Oh, yeah.
Let's do it.
All right,
have a good time.
Not going to find
any clothes in there.
Hey, you guys.
Hi.
Guess who's
up for keynote speaker
at the National
Paleontology Conference?
Uh... Chris Bailey.
Yeah, right.
When was the last time
he made a submission deadline
for an abstract?
( laughing )
Why were you laughing?
Just seeing
what it would be like
to be a paleontologist.
It's fun. Yeah.
So, you're up
for keynote speaker.
Yeah.
Who's making
the decision?
Professor Sherman.
I'm meeting with him today.
He's a pretty tough guy
to impress.
Yeah, well, I think I know
how to dazzle him.
Oh? You're not going to
do a magic trick, are you?
( derisive snort )
No.
Hey, guys.
Wait a minute, you guys.
I want to ask you something.
I may get to speak
at this paleontology convention.
If I do, I'd love for you guys
to come and hear me.
I think
I can safely say
that we all
have family issues,
work stuff,
and/or are sick.
It's in Barbados.
But you come first.
I'm there.
See you later.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
See you.
All right, so,
how did it go
at the fertility clinic?
Not as much fun as last time.
Apparently, you only get porn
if you're giving a sperm sample.
So, uh, so, what
did the doctor say?
Well, there's surrogacy,
but Monica's dreamt her whole
life of carrying a child,
and she just felt
that watching a surrogate
would be too hard for her.
So, you're ruling out
surrogacy?
Yeah.
So I don't have to learn
what that means?
Aside from adoption,
the only other choice
is insemination,
so we're talking
about sperm donors.
Enough said; I'm there
for you, man.
Where is she? Upstairs?
Ah...
How do you feel
about all this?
Well, I wish there was
an easier way for us
to have a child,
but I don't think there is one.
Come on, Ross.
Be a good guy.
Step up and do it.
What?
What? No!
I'm not going
to give them Ben.
The data we're receiving
from MRI scans
and DNA testing of these fossils
are staggering.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, we've
been accepting
Leakey's dates
as a given,
but if they're off
by even 100,000 years or so,
then you can, you can just throw
most of our assumptions,
you know,
right in
the trash.
So... so, what I'm saying,
is... is...
is that...
uh... rah... repercussions
could... could be huge.
I mean, not just
in paleontology,
but if you think about it
in-in evolutionary biology,
uh... genetics, uh... geology.
I mean, truly,
th-the mind boggles.
( snoring )
Well, that's not what you want.
Incentive
for Men?
Oh, I'll take some
of that.
Pheebs,
it's for men.
No, I know,
but this way when I go
to the party later,
Mike will know I'm over him
'cause I'm going to smell
like another guy.
Yeah.
Okay.
( sniffing )
Oh, good.
I'm dating a Russian cabdriver.
Seriously, does
anyone buy this?
I smell like beets.
So, you know what?
I really like those jackets
with the shoulder pads
in them.
Where do you think
those would be?
Um, on Melanie Griffith
in Working Girl.
Um, I think what you
want is over here.
See? I told you
I needed someone.
Oh, you know,
by the way
as a thank you,
I would really love
to take you out.
Really?
Yeah.
Actually, Joey and I
are going to a movie tonight.
Want to come?
Oh, I can't.
Because I-I...
I've seen them.
You've seen...
all the movies?
Yeah. I'm a big fan...
of the movies.
You know,
motion pictures.
The talkies.
Hey, Rach, will you come
with me to a dressing room?
Sure.
Okay.
Well, um, you know,
maybe we can do
something else.
Well, you know,
that depends
on what it is.
I've done a lot of stuff.
So, now what were you doing
out there?
Do you not like Charlie?
She's... she's okay.
I just... I don't know.
I just don't get
a really good vibe from her.
Why?
I don't know.
You know, just the way
she waltzed in here
all smart and... tall,
you know
and just swept Joey
off his feet.
I mean, nobody else
has a chance.
Who else?
Anybody.
You... me...
you know, Monica's mom.
You like Joey?!
Shh... Phoebe.
Oh, all right, I have
a little thing for him.
Just a little.
Oh, my God!
It's just physical
and I have it
totally under control, okay?
It's just... when I see them
together sometimes,
I... I just get
a little jealous.
Well, isn't it ironic
that he liked you
and now you like...
I get it!
All right, as long as it's
under control, you know.
I mean, you can't
do anything about it.
He's already dating her
and she is a nice person.
That wouldn't be right.
I know, I know.
So, it's just
not a big deal.
Yeah.
So, can we keep this between us?
Sure, sure.
Okay, great,
'cause I got to
get out of here.
The smell of beets
is killing me.
Any-any chance
Charlie has a deaf twin?
( groans )
Hi, honey.
Hey.
Look, I brought a friend
home for dinner.
This is Zack from work.
Oh, of course.
It's so nice to see
you again, Zack.
You, too.
You guys haven't
actually met before,
but, boy, are
you both polite.
Why don't you
have a seat, Zack.
I'll get you a beer.
I got it.
Thanks.
So, Zack's
pretty nice, huh?
Yeah, I guess.
So, how would you like
to have a baby
that's half yours
and half his?
Excuse me?
Well, we're talking
about sperm donors
and Zack may be the guy.
I mean, look,
he's intelligent,
he's healthy,
he's athletic...
I mean, he's sperm-tastic.
What...? Chandler,
this is crazy.
What did you
even say to him?
"Come up. Meet my wife.
Give us your sperm."
You know, I invited him
to dinner
so you could get a chance
to get to know him, you know.
I mean, if we go through a sperm
bank, you never meet the guy,
get to check him out.
Chandler...
I'm telling you, he's great.
I mean, even if my sperm
worked fine,
I think he'd be the way to go.
Look, I'm not going
to be a part of this.
You can't just bring
some random guy home
and expect him
to be our sperm donor.
( mockingly ):
O-kay.
Zack.
Thanks.
Do you... do you have a coaster?
I don't want to make a ring.
Tell me about yourself, Zack.
Oh, God, do you
think she heard?
Oh, it'd be so bad
if she heard.
Well maybe she didn't hear.
I'm going to go into
that dressing room,
you stay in here
and I'll talk.
See if you can hear me.
Okay, great.
Oh, thank God,
I can't hear a word
that you're saying.
I didn't
say anything yet.
Well, get back
in there and talk.
I'm Rachel.
It's so annoying when
I put Emma on the phone
to talk with my friends.
What?!
Well, some things are just
hard to say to your face.
Okay, well, I heard that,
which means
that she heard it, too.
We have a problem.
Oh, what are we
going to do?
Just be honest
with her.
Oh, my God.
And it is annoying when parents
put their babies on the phone.
All right, enough out of you!
( phone ringing )
Hello?
( whispering ):
Joey, hey.
I need to talk
to Charlie.
Is she there?
No. She went shopping
with Rachel.
Why? What's up?
Well, I'm meeting
with Professor Sherman
about my being
the keynote speaker...
Oh. How's it going?
It could be better.
He, um, he fell asleep.
What?!
But I already bought my ticket
to Bermuda.
Barbados.
Fine, I'll rent a car and drive.
Look, Ross,
you have to get that job.
What am I
supposed to do?
He's out cold.
In fact, he was
just talking in his sleep before
and evidently, he wants someone
named Fran to spank him harder.
Well, just wake him up.
I can't.
If he realizes that I'm the one
who put him to sleep
I won't get the job.
Ooh, that's a tough one.
Oh, wait a minute.
This happened to me before.
Yeah, I was auditioning
for a play
and the producer fell asleep.
No... wait a minute.
It was me who fell asleep.
Yeah, I mean,
hey, Shakespeare, how 'bout
a chase scene once in a while?
Hey, guys, dinner's ready.
I'm going to go
wash up first.
Thanks.
So, what do you think?
I want this
guy's genes for my kid.
Those eyes, those cheekbones.
Okay, there's enthusiastic
and there's just plain gay.
You don't like him.
I think he's fine,
it's just that we don't know
anything real about him.
I wish we could
get more information.
All right,
just follow my lead.
You guys have such
a great place here.
Oh, thanks, I'm crazy
about our place.
Hey, speaking
of crazy,
do you have a history
of mental illness in the family?
Um, no.
Although I did have an uncle
who voted for Dukakis.
That's really not the kind of
thing we're looking for, Zack.
Okay.
So, um, so tell me,
how'd you guys meet?
Oh, friends first, drunk
in London, you know the story.
I've got a better
question for you.
Do you or any of your blood
relatives have diabetes?
No.
Uh, heart disease,
Alzheimer's, gout?
You guys don't have people
over for dinner a lot, huh?
Oh, we're just
making conversation.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I heard a joke today,
it's pretty funny.
You know what's not funny--
male pattern baldness.
All right,
listen.
You guys have shown
a lot of interest in me tonight
and I'm flattered,
and quite frankly,
a little frightened.
Can we just talk
about something else?
Sure.
All right.
This ravioli's delicious.
I notice you're
enjoying that ravioli
with a beautiful set of teeth.
Did you have braces as a child?
No, I didn't.
Yes!
We're teeth people, Zack.
All right,
let's just do it.
Let's just go over there
and just see if she heard.
Good plan. Okay.
What? Where...
where are you going?
Oh, I'm sorry, Rachel.
I don't have time for your
childish games, okay?
I still have
to go find something
incredible to wear so I can beat
Mike at who's more over who.
Hey, hi, hey,
where have you been?
Oh, trying on clothes.
Oh, re... in the dr...
in the dressing room?
Well, that's so weird.
Phoebe and I were just trying on
clothes in the dressing room.
Gosh, it's such a small world.
Rachel, I heard
you two guys whispering.
Oh, God, you did, you heard.
Okay, let me explain.
No, there's nothing
to explain, I heard you.
Phoebe likes Joey.
Yeah.
I just, I don't understand it.
I mean, Phoebe likes Joey
and then she comes here to buy
a dress to impress another guy?
Yeah, that's Phoebe,
that's Phoebe.
You know,
she just wants them all.
It's like... she's nympho.
Wow.
Yeah.
You know, by the way,
I heard you tell her
not to do anything.
Thanks for sticking up for me.
You are such
a nice person.
I try.
( snoring )
( loud creaking )
Ooh!
Oh, my God.
You really want me to be
the keynote speaker?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wow.
You look... stop eating hot.
Which is, like,
the highest level of hotness.
Okay. Are you sure?
'Cause I am really dreading
going to this party.
Then don't go.
Mike knows I'm coming.
If I don't show up, he'll think
it's 'cause of him.
And then I'm going to lose face.
That's a very serious thing
in my culture.
All right.
Then you go to that party and
you pretend to be over Mike.
And afterward,
you come to my place
and I'll get you good and drunk.
You got it. Okay.
But not on the wine
that you made, okay?
'Cause I just don't want to go
want to the emergency room.
Okay.
David?
Phoebe. Hi.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
You look unbelievable.
Oh, yeah, well...
Wha... what are you doing here?
Well, I'm back from Minsk.
Permanently.
What happened?
Well, remember how I was
trying to achieve
the positronic distillation
of subatomic particles?
Yeah.
Well, after eight years
of research,
I discovered that...
it can't be done.
Well, it's great
that you're back.
How are you?
Good, good.
Life is good.
Good.
Um, well, I'm...
I'm seeing someone.
Oh, good for you.
Yeah. She's also
a scientist.
So she's very smart
and pretty, and...
Well, it's actually
because of you, really,
that we're together.
I saw what you had
with that Mike guy,
and I just said,
boy, I want that.
Mike and I broke up.
You're kidding me.
Because I'm not seeing anybody.
I just totally made that up.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't know why.
I'm sorry. I guess I just
didn't want to lose face.
I understand.
Yeah.
Okay, so then, okay...
So we're both living
in New York...
not seeing anyone.
That's so not like us.
I know.
Well... well, this is
probably a stupid question,
seeing that you
look like that,
but, um, do you have
someplace that you
need to be right now?
Well... no.
Do you want to get a drink?
I'd love to.
Great.
Okay.
Do you smell beets?
Oh, all right,
stay upwind of me.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, there's Phoebe.
Is that Mike she's with?
No, that's David.
There's a third guy?
Tip of the iceberg.
Oh...
I'm going to take off now.
You're going to let me
go home, aren't you?
You sure you don't want
to stick around a little longer?
No, no, I should get home.
I'm kind of tired.
Are you just tired now,
or are you always tired?
'Cause that could be a sign
of clinical depression.
No, it's just tiring having
to figure out the age
at which
all my grandparents died.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Bye.
I think we found our sperm.
He does seem pretty perfect.
Yeah? You think so?
Well, should I ask him?
No.
Why not?
Just because his
great-grandmother was obese?
Our kid's going to get that
from you anyway.
No, that's not it.
It's just that when
we were asking him
all those questions before,
I just...
I just realized I don't care
if he is the most perfect guy
in the world.
He's not you.
Yeah! He's better!
No, he's not.
And if I can't get
pregnant with you,
then I don't want
to get pregnant by him
or anyone else.
Really?
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Thank God.
Because I don't want
to do this either.
I was just doing it
because I thought
that was what
you wanted to do.
I'm the husband--
I'm supposed to bring the sperm.
That is
so sweet.
I love you.
So, you know,
this leaves us with...
Adoption.
How do you feel about that?
I think I feel okay about it.
Actually I think I feel
really good about it.
Me, too.
I want to find a baby
that needs a home,
and I want to raise it with you.
And I want to mess it up
in our own specific way.
So this... this is it?
We're really going to adopt?
Yeah.
Oh, my God, we're going
to be parents!
We are going to be
great parents.
And it could be soon.
I mean, think about it.
Right now, somewhere
out there,
our baby could be
being conceived.
Wait. If we're lucky
and we're really,
really, really quiet,
we may be able to
hear the sound of
a condom breaking.
Hey, Zack.
Hey, Chandler.
Look, I just wanted to apologize
for last night.
I got the feeling we made you
a little uncomfortable.
No, you didn't.
Really?
No, you did.
Yeah, well, my wife and I have
some boundary issues, you know.
Sometimes we ask
inappropriate questions.
We're working on it.
Here are the boards
for Friday's pitch.
Oh, thank you.
You wouldn't know
if Jeanette's planning
on keeping her baby, would you?
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org